{
    "subject": "resource/Subhumans_(Canadian_band)",
    "predicate": "property/pastMembers",
    "object": "Randy Bowman",
    "human_readable": "Subhumans (Canadian band) had a past member named Randy Bowman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.969588041305542,
            "question": "When was Randy Bowman a member of Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9615688323974609,
            "question": "Who is a past member of the Canadian band Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.948394238948822,
            "question": "What was Randy Bowman's role in the band Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9277651906013489,
            "question": "Is Randy Bowman still a member of Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8050214052200317,
            "question": "Where can you find more information about Subhumans and Randy Bowman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7718108296394348,
            "question": "What are some popular songs by Subhumans featuring Randy Bowman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6990640759468079,
            "question": "Are there any other notable past members of Subhumans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6343384981155396,
            "question": "Which country is the band Subhumans from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5019327998161316,
            "question": "Has Randy Bowman been involved in any other musical projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4874191880226135,
            "question": "What genre of music does Subhumans play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Subhumans (Canadian band) had a past member named Randy Bowman.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1695_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Randy Bowman been involved in any other musical projects?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1695_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country is the band Subhumans from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1695_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable past members of Subhumans?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1695_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1695_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information about the Canadian punk rock band The Subhumans, including details on its members. Specifically, in `13.txt` and `2.txt`, it mentions that \"Randy Bowman later went on to form the Vancouver band The Scramblers\" after being a member of The Subhumans. This supports the statement that Randy Bowman was a past member of the Canadian band The Subhumans."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}